<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Mark Ellul&#x27;s thoughts</title>
    <link href="https://markellul.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://markellul.com" />
    <updated>2021-01-01T18:25:02+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Mark Ellul</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://markellul.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Happy New Year 2021</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Ellul</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://markellul.com/happy-new-year-2021.html"/>
        <id>https://markellul.com/happy-new-year-2021.html</id>

        <updated>2021-01-01T18:25:02+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    So a New year, new challenges on their way. Covid-19 is still with us, so I just want to hope that you all&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>So a New year, new challenges on their way. Covid-19 is still with us, so I just want to hope that you all take the necessary precautions for your respective environments. Be Safe and Have Fun, As much as you can!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Publii Impresses</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Ellul</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://markellul.com/publii-impresses.html"/>
        <id>https://markellul.com/publii-impresses.html</id>

        <updated>2020-12-09T19:52:39+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Publii makes creating and deploying a static website, like a blog, a piece of cake. I am a software engineer and whenever&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p> </p>
<p>Publii makes creating and deploying a static website, like a blog, a piece of cake. I am a software engineer and whenever I get caught up in creating a site for myself I get lost in frameworks and and themes, and Publii centralizes all those decisions while still giving me the flexibility to customize to an enormous degree! </p>
<p>The pure simplicity to add a new post and deploy, has inspired me to actually start posting my thoughts...</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Welcome to my Page</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Ellul</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://markellul.com/welcome-to-my-page.html"/>
        <id>https://markellul.com/welcome-to-my-page.html</id>

        <updated>2020-12-07T16:39:24+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Hi, Welcome to this web page, I am Mark Ellul. I have set up this page in part for testing out Github&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    Hi,
  </p>

  <p>
    Welcome to this web page, I am Mark Ellul. I have set up this page in part for testing out <a href="https://github.com" target="_blank">Github</a> Pages and the <a href="https://getpublii.com/" target="_blank">Publii </a>Publishing tool
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
