<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Mark Ellul&#x27;s thoughts</title>
    <link href="https://markellul.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://markellul.com" />
    <updated>2021-03-01T23:55:09+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Mark Ellul</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://markellul.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>The Game of L.I.F.E</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Ellul</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://markellul.com/the-game-of-life.html"/>
        <id>https://markellul.com/the-game-of-life.html</id>

        <updated>2021-03-01T23:55:09+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Welcome New Player....Learn Integration &amp; Feel Everything, in short, LIFE, is the newest full immersion games in the Multiverse. As a new Player,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Welcome New Player....</h2>
<p>Learn Integration &amp; Feel Everything, in short, LIFE, is the newest full immersion games in the Multiverse.</p>
<p>As a new Player, you can decide to join for a solo mission and make friends with other players on the way OR you join in with your friends?</p>
<p>You will then choose what type of experience do you want to have and in what game.</p>
<p>Each game is a set of collective rules made up by everyone who joins that game and that game will have one over all time line. Though many games can spawn from that game when players choose to.</p>
<p>Due our infinite capacity we can have unlimited games all running at once.</p>
<p>In the next chapter we will go into some details about the decisions you need to make before jumping into the Game of L.I.F.E</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Dad Joke</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Ellul</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://markellul.com/dad-joke.html"/>
        <id>https://markellul.com/dad-joke.html</id>

        <updated>2021-02-18T23:25:15+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Daughter walks past Dad and sees his toe sticking out of a sock.... Daughter: Dad you have a hole in your Sock Dad: I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><em>Daughter walks past Dad and sees his toe sticking out of a sock....</em></p>
<p><strong>Daughter: </strong>Dad you have a hole in your Sock</p>
<p class="align-left"><strong>Dad: </strong>I know, the Pope bought them for me.</p>
<p><strong>Daughter: </strong>Really??!!! (face a bit perplexed)</p>
<p><strong>Dad: </strong>These are holy socks....</p>
<p><em>Daughter looks away in disgust and appreciation of the pun!</em></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Nostalgia</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Ellul</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://markellul.com/nostalgia.html"/>
        <id>https://markellul.com/nostalgia.html</id>

        <updated>2021-01-21T22:34:09+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Nostalgia, in these uncertain times can be trap, you might ponder on the good old days and feel worse about your current circumstances.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Nostalgia, in these uncertain times can be trap, you might ponder on the good old days and feel worse about your current circumstances. That said when used positively, You can be thankful for the experiences you have had, that you had the opportunity to live them.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What you do Now will be a memory of your Future self</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Ellul</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://markellul.com/what-you-do-now-will-be-a-memory-of-your-future-self.html"/>
        <id>https://markellul.com/what-you-do-now-will-be-a-memory-of-your-future-self.html</id>

        <updated>2021-01-11T11:30:29+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    What you do now, will be a memory of your future self, the person you are in 5 minutes, or 5 hours or&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>What you do now, will be a memory of your future self, the person you are in 5 minutes, or 5 hours or 5 days... etc</p>
<p>So what do you want to remember about now in the future?</p>
<p>Act NOW in the way that you will feel proud in the future. </p>
<p>Take a second and breath in and breath out, focus on good feeling thoughts, appreciate the now and when you need to take action, think about how you want to remember this action.</p>
<p>Be the best you can be in this now moment, to avoid regret and shame in the the future!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Happy New Year 2021</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Ellul</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://markellul.com/happy-new-year-2021.html"/>
        <id>https://markellul.com/happy-new-year-2021.html</id>

        <updated>2021-01-01T18:25:02+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    So a New year, new challenges on their way. Covid-19 is still with us, so I just want to hope that you all&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>So a New year, new challenges on their way. Covid-19 is still with us, so I just want to hope that you all take the necessary precautions for your respective environments. Be Safe and Have Fun, As much as you can!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Publii Impresses</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Ellul</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://markellul.com/publii-impresses.html"/>
        <id>https://markellul.com/publii-impresses.html</id>

        <updated>2020-12-09T19:52:39+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Publii makes creating and deploying a static website, like a blog, a piece of cake. I am a software engineer and whenever&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p> </p>
<p>Publii makes creating and deploying a static website, like a blog, a piece of cake. I am a software engineer and whenever I get caught up in creating a site for myself I get lost in frameworks and and themes, and Publii centralizes all those decisions while still giving me the flexibility to customize to an enormous degree! </p>
<p>The pure simplicity to add a new post and deploy, has inspired me to actually start posting my thoughts...</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Welcome to my Page</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Ellul</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://markellul.com/welcome-to-my-page.html"/>
        <id>https://markellul.com/welcome-to-my-page.html</id>

        <updated>2020-12-07T16:39:24+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Hi, Welcome to this web page, I am Mark Ellul. I have set up this page in part for testing out Github&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    Hi,
  </p>

  <p>
    Welcome to this web page, I am Mark Ellul. I have set up this page in part for testing out <a href="https://github.com" target="_blank">Github</a> Pages and the <a href="https://getpublii.com/" target="_blank">Publii </a>Publishing tool
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
